You're joining us for hacking augmented reality with connect in the rumah live toolkit
alongside andy wilson I'm ben low-power and we're really excited we
know there's dozens and dozens of options for
you the build viewing audience and andy and I we have
a goal today of making this I think everyone's favorite session...ferret
and what you have to let us now in the comments how we did if we lived up to the goal or not
...were excited to share this with you so this is a quick look
at our agenda we're going to talk about the perspective and how important
is to have perspective in different installations we're going to get right into
it with projection mapping I'm expecting that most of the people out there of heard of connect but we're
going to...we're going to spend sixty second super-high level on
connect we're also then going to talk about actually that point
...going to start talking about some of his research and microsoft research
and projects maybe you've heard of them aluminum and room alive and we're going to get into it with the
...live toolkit we're going to talk about rooms...calibration
great codes and also more on projection mapping
in a ton a demos we got a lot to get through so hold on to your
...we're going to have some fun so let's talk a little bit about what we mean by hacking augmented
reality so maybe you've heard of a...microsoft announced back in january called the hollow
...we talked about...and these really amazing immersive things
that you can do their with how...but the reality is that
artists have been making interactive or I should say they've
been making visually quarrel what's the french I don't know
...you may have trick of the...affects for years so maybe even
centuries...with paint and...so let's take a look at some of these so
shot out to axle p mahler the artist who did this gave us permission to use these
but if you notice here this is a parking garage that he did in sydney it looks as
if the up and out directions are sort of floating in the air and
then the photos at the bottom show how that was actually done so again the
perspective very important for creating this effect ...
pop gave us permission to use his youtube video here again this
reebok's cube with the right perspective looks like an actual rick's cuban
...you the trick is revealed here with the rotation and then finally artist
edgar mueller thank you for...awesome projects
on sidewalks so it really looks like this germans about to fall into this curve
...here's to kids having fun as they you know, go over this
waterfall and then here edgar shows us how it's really done if you're in
the right position and you can see again perspective playing a real important role here
in these effects so again...in paint
are possible but now let's look at projection mapping soif
you look at wikipedia you guys can all go up and look at the wikipedia page I took this from
their the blow-out here the thing that I want to point out is this technique
is also is used by artist and advertisers alike who can add extra dimensions optical
illusions and notions of movement onto previously static
objects static so here's some examples again from wikipedia
page we've got this sculpture on the left adding these this textured look
at this visual look what I'm assuming is a casino here in the middle drawing people
...with projection mapping onto the building and then this other church very cool
...up at night again with projection
mapping but these are static these objects don't move well,
why...important talk about connect here what we're going to add connect into these projection
mapping scenarios here name is going to talk more about this but with the connect we can
make these projection mapping experiences really interactive so,
quickly about the connect if you're new to it we have a really powerful sdk
you can program apps in cplus-plus csharp
actually we were in montreal recently for...and we announce
...connect to project...on get hub today...you're a python developer you can start
...connecting your experiences the connect
sensor gives us data sources we call them we have depth
color infrared and even directional audio we're not going to use the
latter to here we're really focus on depth and color but again the connect gives you all of
those data sources you can also use if you already have an xbox one with
...connect we came out with an adaptor a few months ago that allows you to
plugged into a pc so you can use that and
then also on get hub alive right now we've got this tutorial so
if you're new to connect and you want to get through the entire platform...tutorials really,
really great takes you through all aspects of the platform into and, its
upon get hubs you can go take a look at that and then finally connect for windows dot com if you want
more information download the sdk check out our bloghow we do...felt like about
sixty seconds...I wasn't timing it so I think with that I'm going to handed over to you any
...overhearing drive the slides run
...about some of your work so this is just a preview...some of the things that we're going to be doing withour
new you software but what I'd like to do next is get into a little bit of the some of the
previous work we've done at microsoft research so we've been
while working with projectors in-depth cameras for a little while with projects such as light space...and
one-room room alive bima tran in a few others on the upper right here there's just
a quick of in yet of aluminum room and that's an interesting one that's you
may have seen it uses a single projector a single camera and,
then room alive down below the uses actually six cameras and six
projectors to actually do an entire room we can address both of these scenarios
in the software about to talk about so that software is called the
...live toolkits over happy to announce that today
this is basically a toolkit that allows you to do interactive projection mappings
...for one second because I just want to get this plug-in about how awesome this is
for me so last fall I'm going over to andes office and
...said hey...you guys have all this awesome stuff that you've done using connect
and is there some way that we can make this available to
our broader developer community and those conversations let us to where we are today so
...again I just I...to point out that you were awesome to work...and you had
done all this awesome research so we're really happy to be able to packaged up in this
toolkit and, I can avail awesome...so one of the things
that we've notices that the ...people are struggling out there a little bit to do some of these aluminum
...room alive scenarios by themselves so what
we're providing or some of the tools and we support multiple...multiple projectors together
in the same system and we're focusing today mostly on the calibration
...aspects of it because I think that that's one of the parts the people out there have really have trouble with
artists in
...creative coders and that sort of those kinds of folks have trouble with that
were also delivering a projection mapping set sample
this very simple little sample to shows you what you can do once you have the calibration and this can
be released under the mit license?
And, here's the url for the source code on get
hump go ahead and check that out today and here's just a quick
rundown of the components and how they fit together it's a single visual studio solution everything's written csharp?
we have calibrate ensemble that...which is a program that you run to actually initiate
the calibration it relies on a dl here program
ensemble calibration and furthermore we have a this connect server...which is running
...pc that's hosting a connect camera
...app can then talk to both of these components to pick up the calibration
information and also get the color in-depth information feature cameras on the networking go into this little bit later
in more detail this other executable projector server this is something that we're using
today in calibration and...tidbit pro cam shortened
...camera that's...taken together
projector can-we like long names so projection mapping just this
is a problem statement really just a quick way capsule what it is basically if you have a connect
sensor that sensing the geometry the world and you have a viewer here is
looking at the scene and the teapot here is projected the
problem is given this viewers position and the geometry sense by the connects
...in the fact the projectors actually somewhere else in the room what kind of image
...form on the projectors such that this user from this position has the impression of
their being a teapot sitting on this table...this table...be real so,
you must account for the regularity of the projection surface the...the projector...viewers
...position so that's projection of this with the artist
...and in our software essentially doing with the
artist have been doing the same...calculation by doing...thirty times a second?
So, this is the minimal configuration we think a lot of people are going to be looking at
this because you might have one projector and one connect camera might be less
likely have six cameras and six projectors so it's essentially a connect vtwo
...plugged into a pc and projector plugged into a pc and you have the connect
me to runtime you have this xml file calling ensemble that xml and that
includes all of the calibration information that we're going to generate with our tool and
then your application runs there and the rendering is done locally now
going to m connection n projectors the situation gets a
little more interesting perhaps today we will have support for
a distributing multiple connect sensors across the network each plug into
the its own pc all these guys are plugged in the same switch and then we have
host machine again which does all of the rendering to possibly multiple projectors?
the room diagram so this is basically little bit more of a about the geometry of the connects
and projectors and how they relate to one another so the idea is now we have
projector the projects out into the room we have a connect camera looking out on to that room
...this right now...projector group that's basically a projector
and all of the connect sensors that can see whenever that projector some part of whatever
the projector displays so that's a projector group another projector out
over here some place else in the room might have another connect sensor next to it possibly
a second camera and that would be another group so,
these two groups are distinct there's no way to relate
the geometry is of one group to the other until we actually add a
...another connect camera so now we have three cameras
and to projectors and now this particular camera that we just
...a belongs to both groups and that's actually a critical feature of the calibration
process and...were able to establish the geometry of the
two groups together so we're just in so there's diagrams revise is these
two projector groups so there's these groups actually overlap so taken together we're calling this
an ensemble the two groups so,
let's look into a little bit more detail on some of the components the program,
program ensemble...ideologue is really the core of the project has all
the calibration code and it is using the calibration step
to acquire calibration patterns and calculate the camera parameters of
connection projectors that includes quantities like the focal length and the
...optical center of the camera as well as the dimensions of the
camera so forth these are things you need to in the need to know so it also calculates the
pose that is the position and orientation of all the connects and the projectors?
And, then we...use this deal in runtime to basically provide
a ways to interact with the calibration results and pull out the things you need in order to do
the correct rendering so this is a class library there's no ui to speak of now connect
servers and the another component...
it uses windows communication foundation so we this is basically our tool to
distribute color in data from each camera around the network has no
ui today and basically started up and you forget about it runs on each pc with connect
sensor so in my own work as I find it really heady
to run remote desktop on each of these pc's and then you initiate the connect server
there's a real tip in your already p options be sure to set the audio to
play on remote computer otherwise the connect sdk does not the
plate very nicely and that's a known issue in the connect sdk so if you're going to launch any sort of
...remote desktop you really need to be wary of this consideration
so obviously requires the connect from windows vtwo sdk and it...a
give today gives you access to color depth and the camera interns excess the focal length the
principle point so forth across network in a fairly easy wham.
So, projector server that exes another one
another component that's run on the network and that's analogous to
the connect server directly runs...every machine has a projector
and today we only use that during the calibration step and we're
...delivering a runt a distributed rendering framework today this is
basically a means to calibrate possibly many projectors
...could be the foundation for distributed rendering framework that we might deliver are
the someone could help us out with the idea there would be we can
do something much more like a projectors twelve projectors you probably need to get
off of the same single host pc at that
point so right so if you have more than three projectors calibrate ensemble
...that's a little bit of a ui you can actually do the calibration without any
...a...functions are all there but...things along into
...in configuration we provide a very simple user interfaces
picture here and it runs allows you to run the calibration procedure
...creates this xml file is
stores the calibration info and allows you to view the results so your application
...in xml file and again it does its own rendering today we provide a simple
projection mapping application that includes much of direct three-d eleven shatters
...the rendering including the projection mapping and handling the depth image
in converting the depth image to world coordinates and mash and vertex data.
So, calibration again,
this is all about finding the position impose of every...along with focal length and
...distortion the projectors display...called grey codes and,
these are observed by all the...connects color cameras that way they can
establish the projector groups like what which cameras...which groups with
the projectors and I'm not going to get into the details of how great codes work is very interesting but
...to say that what we're doing here is to is obtaining a series of depth
camera three-d points and...corresponding
position and each of the projector images so that's what you need in order to really
performer calibration the calibration patterns are...to disk you
...run acquisition phase and then disconnect from your network or what
...leave your lab and then you can run the calibration procedure
offlineso, you don't even need access to your cameras in your projectors that
...to play around with the calibration so let's do a quick demo of
the calibration and all right so let's look at the demo the calibration
tool so I'm in visual studio here and I'm just going to hit
...five run the tool this is what it looks like there's not much to see here the first thing we
want to do is hit new this allows us to create a new of xml files
going-to dial-in three projectors and three cameras
...is synonymous with connect here?
That's right...connect sensor and I'm going to create a.
A new folder for this all calibration results are stored in a little folder
going to put here and then I'm going to call that file ...
...go into that folder first and then call that.
Ensemble.
That xml.
Okay, so, that's good so then what I'm
...do is I'm actually...open that up in visual studio so that we can so,
I can show you what that looks like and some resume up just a little bit so you
see this little bit more easily so this is basically layout of this
...file has a number of cameras and projectors listed
okay so for each of these cameras and has a...a friendly name which in the
lab an example I'm going to show you later I have three projectors three cameras and I
call them center-left and rights and then the host name
...address could be something like in the machine happens to be name...zero
notice also the...information here this is actually a four-by-four matrix
that would be familiar to anyone who in using doing graphics programming that's actually
specified here and this file for the very first camera the very first camera
establishes the coordinate system for the entire ensemble so this is filled in for you it
assumes basically that the first...actually at this
...within the global...frame if you had some other reason to establish a
different position for that camera you could fill that information in now for the other cameras
what is it fair to say than like we don't expect these numbers to change post
calibration this is sort of the origin of the whole thing and everything else is going to be calibrated
to that that's right that's right so if you had some other
...sorry some other coordinate system like the room coordinates the, you know,
like if you...actually using this...scenario you might actually have reason to edit
this but that will never change at least for the very first
camera so the other cameras don't have any pose information that can be filled in later so,
I can change that and then writes and that sort of thing and then fill in
...changes from local host?
...was...room alive five.
Remodel if.
Three.
And, then so, that's a for the cameras how the so what I'm going
to do now is open up the projectors...the same sort of scenario here
where I can fill in the third friendly names for the projectors this kind of you
have to changes just really nice to be able to do that and, then the actual within height your refer to
the display dimensions those are things that are will be auto discovered by the projector server that
exiting and then I'm going-to leave these locus right now because we're today we're doing
a local rendering so I hit control the save I
go back to my application and then here there's a reload functionality and then
so, loads that now so, for the purposes of this demonstration
...going to do next is actually we're not going to the trigger the acquisition
phase I can do that here with this option because we don't have the cameras in
the projectors here in the studio today I'm not going to do that so what I'm going to do instead
also want to bore everyone sitting here making him wait a bunch...weight well it all
happens so that's right but what I can do is show you a quick video of what that looks like in the
...so when I hit calibrate acquire this is what happens let me explain what's going on here so we
have three projectors today in this example these are all the same...model they don't have to be the same
...can be different resolutions so forth and then three other connect we
to cameras there and these are just sort of casually place saturn
...any time worrying about mounting and then this otherconnect camera's
actually is almost not use it all...is not even relevant for this calibration is actually
uses a head tracking camera for demo they're going to show later so don't worry too much about that one so,
we need to...the so that they're that they overlap
has explained earlier and I'll show you a little bit what that means.
So, play this video.
...a moment ...these ...going to show that that's
basically just a handy feature for-you to be able to view the results so, it takes
a snapshot from the color camera now the centric projectors now projecting a series of
...code so these are the...codes that you're used to establishes mapping from a pixel
in the color camera to a pixel coordinate in the projected display so,
that's a pretty critical feature so now I've just spent the video up a little bit because
...kind of boring after...you seen a couple these so,
you just let this thing run and then after a few minutes...it finishes so that's the acquisition
face without point so, that point we have.
Stop this and I'll show you a little bit what we have with
someone switch now to this other calibration which
is like cooking show right where that we pulled the thing out of the evidence magically done so,
we have a...xml file here which now has a bit more information
has things like the color camera matrix in this kinds of things, things that are pull off of each of
the connect cameras and then also windows this directory layout...if we really want
to get into the directory layout but let me real quickly just show a couple of things that so,
we have directory for each of the cameras...a directory for each of the projectors the
camera includes things like the just the color image make that little
bit larger and the mean depth image so forth so you can that's kind of useful
to see what's going on there the projector directory now has directory within
within it for each camera intern and that includes the
gray codes as viewed from each of the cameras for that projector so,
that's so, that's basically all store on-disk so it's kind of a large directory so if we move
over to the left camera you'll see that as a
slightly skewed perspective now because you reviewing the center projector from the left cameras so you would
expectto not be able to see the entire projected
...important that the one of the camera...of the other camera's actually be able to see part of that
projector ok so that's the directory so now at this point but, so, after the acquisition
phase runs all that's created and then the ensemble dot xml
is updated to have all of those interns x in there and that's what that's really
the,...just as intrinsic now for the connect...connect
...so we haven't actually performed any calibration yet so we've just on acquisition we've gotten some of the
information we need now we need to go back to the tool going to open up that particular.
Calibration set-up that we were looking for.
Looking at and the load that one and,
then I would now hit solve oddity.
Calibrate menu is going to open that up a so,
this is kicking off now the actual calibration and you can see what's going on here is decoding the
great code image...those off of disk for each of the views so there's three cameras three
...so that's nine sets.
And,...it takes a little, little bit of time and then the next phase where it actually performs bit of
analysis determine the visibility so it...projector center here is seen by
...center projector...seen my camera left and camera right
so that's interesting so now we have the center projector and the projector group
...of the sent the center projector group includes all three cameras so this is like the bridge
...thing that establishes...glue.
Between all three cameras in the three projectors we also
have the left camera or the left projector and the right projector so this next
bit here shows the actual camera matrix associated with the projector so,
that includes the focal length of the projector and also the center from
...optics point of view the optical center the projector
...numbers...kind of funny the optical center is so there's a twelve
...by seven twenty projector which puts the middle the x coordinate the horizontal axis
at about six twenty which seems reasonable but then...negative values really interesting and
that's because when you look at the projector the optical center
is actually...this is why when you put projector down
the desktop it actually doesn't project into the desktop but above it only uses the top half of the
...so that's why
those that numbers negative anyway so this is getting into a little bit maybe...more
...you need to understand the tool but it's kind of interesting to look at these kinds of things
and the reason why we're sort of dumping
...stuff out is so that we can take a look at what's going on so that's going to run for a while it
performs a calibration for each of the projector groups
intern so that's...be running for three times and then actually does a
much more involved global optimization over all the
cameras and projectors to establish just make sure that everything's nice and, ...
So,...let that run now for a little while but what I can
...can...well that's running is because this is actually a fully baked.
See what I think I'll do is stop the.
This calibration...by exiting the program and then.
We loading that one.
Then I'll show you a little bit of the results are kind of fun
to look at so this other pain...I haven't mentioned
is showing you remember it flashed up those images for the each projector that had the projector name
it also has the radical for each of those so, we have so,
I can use the wa...and, the mouse the to rotate also
...ctwo to move up and down in the scene so this shows us the data that's collected color...data
merge for each route for all three projectors and cameras...you get an idea of
...quality of the registration it's not too bad, you know, we're not we're not doing any color
calibration so there's a little bit of color...camera has its own white balance so,
that's something we can look at in the future.
So, then this menu appear deserves some comments so right now this graphics
...under a fairly traditional perspective graphics camera
but because we know the part of now the camera matrix reach of
the projectors we can actually dial-in a completely different projection matrix that goes with
each of the projectors so I think this is really interesting viewed sort of
...shows you the quality of the registration for the to projector because what does
...view shows you is view of the room.
From the projectors point of view now because it's a color image
acquired from the connect sensor it's actually that image was actually
...from some other place...not at the same places the projector could be on the other side
of the room so we're using all of the math we just did
to synthesize what that image would look like from the projectors point of
view so this these words here the center and then this radical here
...sort of running along the outside is not rendered by this graphics this
routine here but is really captured in baked into the color image so we would if
everything's working really well we respect this radical now to line-up fairly precisely with
the edges of the frame because of the perspective the projection matrix is basically
set to...that of the projector so,
that's all very difficult to follow just I think the things are too so,
just to look at is the fact that when I match the, you know,
the projection of the projector...using the word projection
into different sensors little bit confusing we now have fairly decent alignment so we can also
check out the same thing for the left projector and then
for the right projector so everything's looking really good and
it's pretty tight actually the zs things go so?
I think that is enough demo for of the calibration tool
Back to.
It's...on turn back to the presentation...where we were.
So, what I'd like to do now is show a quick,
yeah, so, the show a quick a couple demos from our sample so we what
we've done is deliver a very simple projection mapping sample
...shows to main effects ...
The calibration phases like sort of completely separate from the projection mapping but we think a lot of people going
to be using the calibration results do projection mapping as
with womb alive and aluminum so one of the more popular effects and aluminum was
as wobble effect so when you actually fired a gun in the game the whole role
...kind of distort momentarily is really kind of interesting effect and
it was done basically by...taking the color images sense but the connect
center which was done offline and projecting that back with a little bit of edge enhancement color enhancement
and then distorting it in our sort of interesting real-time fashion
so I basically very quickly re implement that for this setup so,
...aluminum just use one camera one projector here we're actually using three so,
we're getting a similar kind of effect but on a broader scale so in caps as more the more
of the room now I don't have the audio...the game or anything like that so it's a little little
contrived maybe but it does give you an idea of some of the alignments so,
quality alignment and some of the things that we can do so of course instead of
...wobble effect you could imagine doing any sort of artistic
sharing on your environment so this is not alive image where this is just a
...with...lumen room so we're not what taking live data hear from the each of the
sensors and then projecting that back but will demonstrate that in a moment.
the second example is the three-d object...so this is a more about
rendering a three-d object hovering in space in front of you and doing the correct
...dependent rendering for that so using...the very same projection mapping
shatter as we use for the wobble effect now rendering a three-d object so,
the geometry years very simple of the sample includes and ...file loader
there's nothing terribly interesting about that does not really the point what we're doing here so now we're
using the this camera to actually do a bit of head tracking so it's a pretty pretty easily get
going with had tracking...dependent rendering...in as the head position and then as I move around
...get to see different parts of the model and notice also that the
...projector set...up so that it projects into the corner of the room which in some
ways...like kind of the most difficult scenario normally
...projector it projects onto a flat wall in your room here
...projecting right in the corner and but for a little bit of distortion
there in the corner it actually looks pretty straight these lines...pretty straight...you looks correct.
Notice also that it's a it's quite a large display
...in accomplices quite a big partner visual field of view.
So, that's the that's the sum of our
and, we just say like even though we're shipping both of those as a single sample.
I think you could also say those are two different samples because there's very different but we've just package those up
right now and that's running them as a single sample in there that's what they use the same sweet of
...three-d...so, it's actually there's a lot more common so each of these
...than you might think so the basic calculation that is doing is pretty much the same,
yeah, one thing to add is that with
the three-d object rendering that we're looking at here I wasn't actually in the lab when you
were shooting the video but if I ran through the scene in there if
I got in there and jumped in you would see this object
then projected not only on the walls on the furniture but also on to me, yeah,
that's a great point of thanks for mentioning that
it's really important point to remember that this in this particular example is the depth and
color who actually just the depth information in this case is being read...from you to the three cameras
and real-time so that if I if somebody walked into the scene...moved to this chair,
for example, it would update in real-time you wouldn't the viewer...not really notice
the difference would it would it would just sort of take that and stride I think that's one of the ways that
the system differs from some of the projection mapping software that's out there already typically
with the projection mapping software out there is not a three-d problem it's like you've taken of uni
know the position of the camera you shooting a large building sarah church as
...the...example we showed the church isn't moving so you can establish
...really what amounts to a tutti transform
the maps the desired view to the different components of the
...facade so that's some that's in some sense a and easier
...what we're doing here on the other hand having the three-d data from connect also
make some of these calculations quite easy to do it's really
...question finding the correct graphics transforms coordinate transforms to make all
...stuff possible so right so with interactive projection map interactive
in the sense that you can go and move things around and it's all being done every
...essentially...new problem we're doing it again as I said earlier we're doing that projection mapping problem the
...of done essentially...video...
So, that's
the sample just a quick few words about future work before we close.
There's...to be done, you know, the source code is certainly still very much influx
I'm making changes all the time some of the higher-level things that...would be nice
to see right now we have a connect server implementation that really is just
tune so that I can get the calibration work done it's not a full implementation
there's lots of things missing like there's no support for the body tracking in the server ir image
...that's pretty...so we could put that in any time something a little more
challenging probably interesting to a lot of people out there is
support for unity so we in our own work we say with
...room...some of the other newer projects we've been moving some of our rendering to unity and
...entails some interesting challenges and working with all of the stuff that we use
we're using the same calibration routines so the idea would be would be to have unity three-d plug-in
allows us to median that xml file and then use all of a unity
...goodness in terms of rendering...loading models and animation so forth
...that's really nice because then you can take all the calibration stuff that
you've done and throw this at an artist somebody who really knows how to generate assets
and they can as we've seen in our own work they can make progress very quickly.
Harder saying is doing proper blending at...you go back and look at some of the videos
we...showed you'll notice that we don't handle the case where the
to projectors overlap very well they essentially
the project twice over that scene so you actually see some brighter images
are brighter areas there were actually projecting twice over the
same little area now that's something I think really needs to be...other people that are
looked at projector blending if you wanted to set up a bunch of projectors and then and then project
onto a flat surface this is a little more challenging here now because everything is in three-d and
as we were just talking about everything is interactive three-d things can change so it's not
as question of finding a single static way to carve up the projected images
you actually have to change that and real-time because as things move
let's say forwards backwards and from the camera that the place where you want to carve up the
projection actually changes so it's a harder problem and that's something that would have to be
computed sort of on-the-fly perhaps best computed one of the shatters so I think the whole
...harder thing actually is to nail the color calibration
think it's pretty obvious and some of the examples that the color we're not
...color calibration at all so, there's a couple of issues
there's one is the color calibration the projection color calibration of the
cameras right now the cameras all have their own white balance need to nail that down another
perhaps more interesting the problem is the fact that we're projecting onto real-world
environment's like say the couch or your rug wall whatever
...be nice to actually compensate for the surface reflections and the color of those objects
...actually generating graphics...a little bit of that
no one-room is very simplistic other much more interesting
and capable models out there and we've got none of that stuff right now in the
room alive toolkit so that's something that we nice to the app so ...go
out there and start projection mapping there's the...again...source code and you know,
show us what you create send us twitter or however whatever communication
...you like what we're open to feature requests issues and
...requests and again,
here's the connect btwo sdk url and I think that's all
...today I think there's one more plug that I forgot to make earlier if you go
out to projection hyphen mapping dot org right...
dave...it's a group of guys of done and...they're
doing a really awesome job bringing all these cool images and videos
of people doing very cutting-edge projection mapping work so again projection hyphen
mapping dot org if you want to get some inspiration and see some of the things that people are doing in this
so, thanks-again for watching and please check out the project on get hub
...your comments and hopefully you have some fun with
...interactive projection mapping.
Great possum thank you.